<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Tony Xu Blog</title><link>https://tonyxu.io/</link><description>Recent content on Tony Xu Blog</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://tonyxu.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Chapter 1 - Reliable, Scalable, and Maintainable Applications</title><link>https://tonyxu.io/books/designing-data-intensive-applications/chapter-1/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tonyxu.io/books/designing-data-intensive-applications/chapter-1/</guid><description>Three concerns that are important in most software systems:
Reliability The system should continue to work correctly even when things go wrong.
Scalability As the system grows, there should be reasonalbe ways of dealing with that growth.
Maintainability Over time, many different people will work on the system, and they should all be able to work on it productively.</description></item><item><title>Chapter 3 - Controlling Execution</title><link>https://tonyxu.io/books/thinking-in-java/chapter-3/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tonyxu.io/books/thinking-in-java/chapter-3/</guid><description>Control statements:
if-else while do-while for return break true and false All conditional statements use truth or falsehood of a conditional expression to determine the execution path.
Number can&amp;rsquo;t be used as boolean, alternative way: if (a!=0)
if-else Two forms of using if:
if(Boolean-expression) statement or
if(Boolean-express) statement else statement Iteration Iteration statements (looping):
while do-while for while while(Boolean-expression) statement do-while do statement while(Boolean-expression) for for(initialization; Boolean-expression; step) statement The comma operator Using the comma operator, you can define multiple variables within a for statement, but they must be of the same type.</description></item><item><title>Saying goodbye to Microsoft</title><link>https://tonyxu.io/reads/2019-05-13/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tonyxu.io/reads/2019-05-13/</guid><description>Saying goodbye to Microsoft - What I gained, lost &amp;amp; learned while working for Microsoft. (medium.com)
It wasn’t a ‘golden cage’ I was in, it was a bubble of illusions that popped once I signed my dismissal papers. Illusions of importance, mission, friendships and luxury.
I’m 28, have learned to put myself first and spent plenty of time on self care, enough to be able to share this publicly and hopefully not to make the same mistakes in the future.</description></item><item><title>Why Google+ Failed</title><link>https://tonyxu.io/reads/2019-04-05/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tonyxu.io/reads/2019-04-05/</guid><description>Why Google+ Failed (onezero.medium.com)
Google Plus didn’t fail because Facebook is invulnerable. It failed because of deep flaws embedded in it from the very start.
It&amp;rsquo;s no news that Google is shutting down its products or services. The author worked in Google+ team and has seen how Google+ end up being one of those. He not only told us the issues and problems that caused the failure, but also what prevented it from being fixed or corrected along the way from product perspective.</description></item><item><title>Chapter 2 - Everything Is an Object</title><link>https://tonyxu.io/books/thinking-in-java/chapter-2/</link><pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tonyxu.io/books/thinking-in-java/chapter-2/</guid><description>The Java language assumes that you want to do only object-oriented programming, so (almost) everything in Java is an object.
You manipulate objects with references You treat everything as an object, using a single consistent syntax. Although you treat everything as an object, the identifier you manipulate is actually a &amp;ldquo;reference&amp;rdquo; to an object.
For example:
String s; You must create all the objects When you create a reference, you want to connect it with a new object.</description></item><item><title>Chapter 1 - Introduction to Objects</title><link>https://tonyxu.io/books/thinking-in-java/chapter-1/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tonyxu.io/books/thinking-in-java/chapter-1/</guid><description>The progress of abstraction Five basic characteristics of object-oriented programming:
Everything is an object. A program is a bunch of objects telling each other what to do by sending messages. Each object has its own memory made up of other objects. Every object has a type All objects of a particular type can receive the same messages. An object has an interface The interface determines what request you can make for a particular object.</description></item><item><title>Stop Learning Frameworks</title><link>https://tonyxu.io/reads/2019-03-15/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tonyxu.io/reads/2019-03-15/</guid><description>Stop Learning Frameworks (sizovs.net)
The longer a technology is on the market, the safer investment it is.
Don’t rush to learn new technology – it has a high probability of dying.
Time will show which technology is worth investing in. Time is your best advisor. Learn to wait.
Remember – frameworks, libraries and tools come and go. Time is precious.
I loves to learn new technologies, which often turned out to be just learning new frameworks/tools.</description></item><item><title>Top Engineering Blogs from Tech Companies to Follow in 2019</title><link>https://tonyxu.io/posts/2019/top-engineering-blogs-from-tech-companies-to-follow-in-2019/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tonyxu.io/posts/2019/top-engineering-blogs-from-tech-companies-to-follow-in-2019/</guid><description>Here is a list of top engineering blogs from tech companies that I follow. I learn how the tech companies build technology infrastructure with high performance, high scalability, and high availability and their best practices summarized along with building the infrastructure.
I subscribed the blogs using RSS reader and read the update everyday.
(in alphabetical order)
Airbnb Engineering &amp;amp; Data Science Bitly Engineering Blog Dropbox Tech Blog Etsy - Code as Craft Facebook Code - Facebook Engineering Blog code.</description></item><item><title>Microservice Architecture at Medium</title><link>https://tonyxu.io/reads/2019-03-09/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tonyxu.io/reads/2019-03-09/</guid><description>Microservice Architecture at Medium (medium.engineering)
At Medium, our technical stack started with a monolithic Node.js app back in 2012. We have built a couple of satellite services, but we haven’t created a strategy to adopt the microservice architecture systematically. As the system becomes more complex and the team grows, we moved to a microservice architecture in early 2018. In this post, we want to share our experiences of doing it effectively and avoiding microservice syndromes.</description></item><item><title>This Is Silicon Valley</title><link>https://tonyxu.io/reads/2019-03-06/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tonyxu.io/reads/2019-03-06/</guid><description>This Is Silicon Valley (onezero.medium.com)
Everyone wears Patagonia and North Face, everyone has AirPods hanging from their ears, and everyone goes to Lake Tahoe on weekends. And everyone talks about the same things: startups, blockchain, machine learning, and startups with blockchain and machine learning.
As Jeffrey Hammerbacher, a former Facebook executive, told Bloomberg, “The best minds of my generation are thinking about how to make people click ads.”
The Silicon Valley author described is exactly what I see in the Silivon Valley.</description></item><item><title>UTC is Enough for Everyone, Right?</title><link>https://tonyxu.io/reads/2019-03-03/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tonyxu.io/reads/2019-03-03/</guid><description>UTC is Enough for Everyone, Right? (zachholman.com)
It turns out humans have had a long, long history of poorly dealing with time, so when you hammer your head against the wall trying to deal with a timezone bug, well, you’re just the last in a long, long line of human beings that are terrible at all this! Congrats. You’re pretty unremarkable.
The author talks about long history of time and how horrible we have been dealing with time.</description></item><item><title>My Productivity Tools and Development Setup Recommended to Software Engineers</title><link>https://tonyxu.io/posts/2019/my-productivity-tools-and-development-setup-recommended-to-software-engineers/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tonyxu.io/posts/2019/my-productivity-tools-and-development-setup-recommended-to-software-engineers/</guid><description>Hardware Laptop 👉 Apple MacBook Pro (13-inch, 2017, Four Thunderbolt 3 Ports) 13-inch 2017 Year 3.5 GHz Intel Core i7 Processor 16 GB Memory 256 GB Storage My MacBook Pro (company provided) is the top 1 productivity tool for me. I use it to code, write blogs, and everything. Mobile Phone 👉 Apple iPhone X I&amp;rsquo;m using iPhone X as my mobile phone. I have been an iPhone person ever</description></item><item><title>Use GitHub for Knowledge Base and Projects Management</title><link>https://tonyxu.io/posts/2019/use-github-to-mange-personal-knowledge-base/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tonyxu.io/posts/2019/use-github-to-mange-personal-knowledge-base/</guid><description>GitHub has become the one and only platform for developers. We collaborate on the platform for anything about code. Can GitHub help you anything else besides code? I have recently been frustrated choosing a tool to manage my personal knowledge base, although there are lots of choices such as note apps (Bear, Evernote), project management app (Trello), or knowledge management app (Notion.so), eventually GitHub turned out to my choice which has below pros:</description></item><item><title>Technologies Learned as a Software Engineer</title><link>https://tonyxu.io/posts/2018/technologies-learned-as-a-software-engineer/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tonyxu.io/posts/2018/technologies-learned-as-a-software-engineer/</guid><description>As a software engineer, I&amp;rsquo;m always excited in learning various new technologies. In this blog, I&amp;rsquo;ll keep a list of technology subjects I have already started learning or plan to learn in my life as a software engineer.
Note: I will keep updating this page as I&amp;rsquo;m learning them
How I scale level of expertise for a technology:
⭒⭒⭒⭒⭒ (Newbie) - New to the technology ⭑⭒⭒⭒⭒ (Beginner) - Understand basic techniques and concepts ⭑⭑⭒⭒⭒ (Novice) - Gained exeprience in class and experiments ⭑⭑⭑⭒⭒ (Intermediate) - Can apply the technology in practice and know its trade-offs ⭑⭑⭑⭑⭒ (Advaned) - Applied the technology in production without assistance and recognized as a go-to person ⭑⭑⭑⭑⭑ (Expert) - Known as an expert, can provide guidance and coach others in the same field Web Development React: ⭑⭑⭑⭒⭒ Angular: ⭑⭑⭒⭒⭒ Node.</description></item><item><title>Embed Google Analytics Dashboard on Website</title><link>https://tonyxu.io/posts/2018/embed-google-analytics-dashboard-on-website/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tonyxu.io/posts/2018/embed-google-analytics-dashboard-on-website/</guid><description>&lt;p>If you are using Google Analytics to analyze site traffic, you might want to embed those amazing dashboards to your website publicly. While Google doesn&amp;rsquo;t provide iframe solution, it does offer a &lt;a href="https://developers.google.com/analytics/devguides/reporting/embed/v1/">Google Analytics Embed API&lt;/a> which requires a bit more technical knowledge. I&amp;rsquo;ll walk you through each and every step and make sure you don&amp;rsquo;t have to read all developer documentation and can easily build dashboard&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Preview:&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="./Analytics_-_Tony_Xu_2018-10-16_09-52-42.png" alt="preview">&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Use Firebase Cloud Function to Count Website Visitors</title><link>https://tonyxu.io/posts/2018/use-firebase-cloud-function-to-count-website-visitors/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tonyxu.io/posts/2018/use-firebase-cloud-function-to-count-website-visitors/</guid><description>It&amp;rsquo;s getting popular to use Firebase hosting to host static website, however, you might not know you can still have server-side code hosted in Firebase for your static website, and that is the Firebase Cloud Function. Once of the case you might want to use the Cloud Function is to write something to Firebase database, for example, a hit counter. In this topic, I&amp;rsquo;ll show you how to use Firebase Cloud Function and Firebase Realtime Database to count website visitor.</description></item><item><title>Customize Chrome New Tab Page</title><link>https://tonyxu.io/posts/2018/customize-chrome-new-tab-page/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tonyxu.io/posts/2018/customize-chrome-new-tab-page/</guid><description>Have you thought about customizing Chrome new tab page? If so, you must have tried the extensions in Chrome web store to customize your new tab page. If you are not satisfied with any of them, you have the option to build your own new tab page that meets all your expectations.
Chrome extension file structure └── chrome-extention //You project directory ├── manifest.json //Chrome extension manifest └── newTab.html //Chrome extension new tab html page Create Chrome extension manifest Create a folder as the project folder for Chrome extension.</description></item><item><title>Why we need to deprecate x prefix for HTTP headers?</title><link>https://tonyxu.io/posts/2018/http-deprecate-x-prefix/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tonyxu.io/posts/2018/http-deprecate-x-prefix/</guid><description>In June, 2012, Internet Engineering Task Force released a new RFC(RFC-6648), recommending deprecation of X- prefix. As LinkedIn also use this type of prefix, I was interested to read this RFC, and explain to you why we need to deprecate it.
X- prefix background HTTP header is used to transmit additional information between client and server.
Some standard HTTP header:
Authorization: Often used to transmit OAuth access token or other authorization information.</description></item><item><title>Write script to scrap house rent price and send to your phone</title><link>https://tonyxu.io/posts/2018/write-script-to-scrap-house-rental-price/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tonyxu.io/posts/2018/write-script-to-scrap-house-rental-price/</guid><description>House rental is a critical thing if you are living in the silicon valley. I&amp;rsquo;m planning to move to a new apartment, but the price changes often. I want to monitor the price and book it when it drops. In order to do that, I wrote a script to monitor the house rental price and push the result to my phone like below.
Get Started The apartment I&amp;rsquo;m looking at is a professional rental apartment, to not disclose the place I will be living in, I&amp;rsquo;m using another one for example.</description></item><item><title>Ultimate way to beautify Mac terminal (oh-my-zsh) and plugin recommendations</title><link>https://tonyxu.io/posts/2018/ultimate-way-to-beautify-mac-terminal-and-recommendations-for-plugins/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tonyxu.io/posts/2018/ultimate-way-to-beautify-mac-terminal-and-recommendations-for-plugins/</guid><description>If you are using Mac as development machine, Terminal.app must be one of the most used apps. Terminal might be not fancy to begin with, but you can totally make it more elegant and fancy if you follow with me.
We will be doing these for our Terminal Install Terminal Profile: Customize Terminal Color Install oh-my-zsh: Use powerful zsh for Terminal, instead of shell Install oh-my-zsh themes: Beautify oh-my-zsh Instal oh-my-zsh must-have plugins: Get more advanced and convenient features for Terminal Preparation Recommend to install homebrew first:</description></item><item><title>The OAuth2 flow for native apps: PKCE</title><link>https://tonyxu.io/posts/2018/oauth2-pkce-flow/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tonyxu.io/posts/2018/oauth2-pkce-flow/</guid><description>If you are building a native application, and you need OAuth 2.0, PKCE OAuth is your best choice. Here I will explain why.
Native application is often used to refer to native application that has no back-end, and running totally in user&amp;rsquo;s devices such as Windows, Mac, iOS, and Android, where securely storing secrets is impossible.
What are the OAuth 2 options for those native applications and what are the pros and cons for them?</description></item><item><title>Use GitLab-CI to run free scheduled jobs</title><link>https://tonyxu.io/posts/2018/use-gitlab-ci-to-run-free-scheduled-jobs/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tonyxu.io/posts/2018/use-gitlab-ci-to-run-free-scheduled-jobs/</guid><description>In this topic, I&amp;rsquo;ll introduce how to run scheduled job with GitLab-CI, without the need to have a server running cron job or other application.
GitLab-CI is a continuous integration/deployment tool, it will trigger some scripts (such as build, test, deployment) when there is new deployment or defined interval. GitLab-CI has a free quota of 2,000 minutes running time, which is 1 hour everyday.
If you prefer GitHub than GitLab, Travis CI also offers similar tool for free.</description></item><item><title>Use IcoMoon to reduce 98% FontAwesome load size</title><link>https://tonyxu.io/posts/2018/use-icomoon-to-reduce-fontawesome-size/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tonyxu.io/posts/2018/use-icomoon-to-reduce-fontawesome-size/</guid><description>FontAwesome is an awesome font library. With fontawesome, it will be super easy to inject icon into your html page. Although the default method is very simple, it has the drawback of taking too much load by loading full set of icons.
In this article, I&amp;rsquo;ll share how I reduce the fontawesome library size by using IcoMoon to generate icon library that only has what I need.
FontAwesome Default Usage Include FontAwesome Icon Library:</description></item><item><title>Be prepared for your next job</title><link>https://tonyxu.io/posts/2018/be-prepared-for-your-next-job/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tonyxu.io/posts/2018/be-prepared-for-your-next-job/</guid><description>This is a presentation shared in DBL retreat. I posted content here for everyone to take a look.
Thanks for reading this blog. In this blog I want to share my personal experience on changing my job and some of my thinking that might be helpful for you. I&amp;rsquo;ll keep this blog in high level, and will not talk about job seeking skills, etc.
I will talk about:</description></item><item><title>Tech stack to build your own product</title><link>https://tonyxu.io/posts/2018/tech-stack-for-building-your-own-product/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tonyxu.io/posts/2018/tech-stack-for-building-your-own-product/</guid><description>As a software engineer or developer, you might want to build a product end-to-end. These are the frameworks and technologies you might need. All listed items are open-source or free to use. Web Front-end Fundamental Language: HTML, JavaScript, CSS Advanced Language: ES6, TypeScript, CoffeScript JS Library/Framework: React, Vue, Angular, jQuery Template Engine: Mustache, Handlebars, Jade CSS Library/Framework: Global: Bootstrap, Foundation, Semantic China: Element, Ant Design, Amaze UI Framework-Specific: Material-UI (React),</description></item><item><title>Use Telegram and Flask to build personal notification server</title><link>https://tonyxu.io/posts/2018/use-telegram-and-flask-to-build-notification-server/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tonyxu.io/posts/2018/use-telegram-and-flask-to-build-notification-server/</guid><description>Imagine if you are in these situations:
I want to notify my girl friend whenver I leave company or arrive home I want to get notified when there is new visit to my website I want get notified when a scraper or job finished The solution to above situations is a mechanism to send message to your phone programmatically and here is my solution:
Build a Flask app to receive GET or POST request, and then compose different messages according to event type and send to some chat channel such as Telegram or Slack.</description></item><item><title>Cloud Computing Explorations</title><link>https://tonyxu.io/posts/2018/cloud-computing-exploration/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tonyxu.io/posts/2018/cloud-computing-exploration/</guid><description>Talking about my experience with cloud computing, the first experience is when I&amp;rsquo;m in 11th grade, deploying a proxy application in Google App Engine to get over the Great Fire Wall in China. Later when I&amp;rsquo;m a freshman in college, I built a website for fun and subscribed shared hosting online. However, I found out that shared hosting has too many restrictions such as you have no control over softwares, so I switched to VPS.</description></item><item><title>Create Alfred workflow for uploading screenshot to S3</title><link>https://tonyxu.io/posts/2018/create-alfred-workflow-for-uploading-screenshot-to-s3/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tonyxu.io/posts/2018/create-alfred-workflow-for-uploading-screenshot-to-s3/</guid><description>As Markdown markup language gets more and more popular, most people have a need to quickly generate a public url for screenshot/image in clipboard. Today I created an Alfred workflow that helps you upload images/screenshot in clipboard. Demo Overview Use pngpaste to get image data from clipboard Write to a image file in /tmp folder Use boto3 to upload image file to AWS S3 Implementation Now we have the idea</description></item><item><title>One month summary for joining LinkedIn</title><link>https://tonyxu.io/posts/2018/join-linkedin-one-month-summary/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tonyxu.io/posts/2018/join-linkedin-one-month-summary/</guid><description>Today is my so-called one month anniversary at LinkedIn. It&amp;rsquo;s been a fast week, bootcamp, Inday, and a week of shutdown. So it&amp;rsquo;s actually much less than a month.
The main thing on my list this month is to get familiar with the technology, tool, process, and products in LinkedIn. Although there is not a lot of happening, I should still look back and think about what can be improved.</description></item><item><title>Improve problem-solving skill</title><link>https://tonyxu.io/posts/2018/improve-your-ability-to-solve-problem-at-work/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tonyxu.io/posts/2018/improve-your-ability-to-solve-problem-at-work/</guid><description>Problem-solving skill is the most important skill at work, you need to think about:
If you are not good at solving problem How to improve the problem-solving skill Look back to the two years working at Moxtra, the fundamental job I do is to solve problem, given that i&amp;rsquo;m a Solution Engineer. And the problem is basically:
I have problem A, do you have solution B? In most cases, I will evaluate based on these aspects:</description></item><item><title>REST API Design Interview Preparation</title><link>https://tonyxu.io/posts/2018/rest-api-design-interview-preparation/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tonyxu.io/posts/2018/rest-api-design-interview-preparation/</guid><description>REST API has become a very popular concept for designing back-end service interface. Most platforms provide REST API as unified interface for web/native applications. If you are going to interview for a job that will require REST API knowledge, you are encouraged to be well prepared for it. Below is my own summary for REST API interview. Hopefully it&amp;rsquo;s helpful for you as well.
Principle Self-describing Simple Safe Preparation (WHO) Identify users Internal or External Roles (Developer, Admin, Customer, Support&amp;hellip;) (HOW) Identify scenario, use cases (WHAT) What functionality or resource will be exposed by API Clarify and confirm above and continue to API design Note:</description></item><item><title>Preface</title><link>https://tonyxu.io/posts/2018/get-started/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tonyxu.io/posts/2018/get-started/</guid><description>Today, I decided to start this blog, which I hope can encourage me to think more and summarize more for my work and life.</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>https://tonyxu.io/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tonyxu.io/about/</guid><description>Hey there, I&amp;rsquo;m Tony Xu, currently working for LinkedIn as a Software Engineer. I love technology and always follow the advancements in technology, especially in the topic of web, mobile, and AI. I have a passion for designing and creating things, notably with code. When I&amp;rsquo;m not coding, I enjoy travelling with family and make travel videos. I live in the San Francisco bay area with my fiancée Helen.
I started this blog in 2018.</description></item><item><title>Analytics</title><link>https://tonyxu.io/analytics/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tonyxu.io/analytics/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Friends</title><link>https://tonyxu.io/friends/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tonyxu.io/friends/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Referral</title><link>https://tonyxu.io/refer/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tonyxu.io/refer/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Search</title><link>https://tonyxu.io/search/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tonyxu.io/search/</guid><description/></item></channel></rss>