<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>推荐阅读 on Tony Xu 博客</title>
    <link>https://tonyxu.io/zh/reads/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 推荐阅读 on Tony Xu 博客</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://tonyxu.io/zh/reads/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>停止学习框架</title>
      <link>https://tonyxu.io/zh/reads/2019-03-15/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tonyxu.io/zh/reads/2019-03-15/</guid>
      <description>Stop Learning Frameworks (sizovs.net) The longer a technology is on the market, the safer investment it is. Don’t rush to learn new technology – it has a high probability of dying. Time will show which technology is worth investing in. Time is your best advisor. Learn to wait. Remember – frameworks, libraries and tools come and go. Time is precious. 我非常热爱学</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Medium的微服务架构</title>
      <link>https://tonyxu.io/zh/reads/2019-03-09/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tonyxu.io/zh/reads/2019-03-09/</guid>
      <description>Microservice Architecture at Medium (medium.engineering) At Medium, our technical stack started with a monolithic Node.js app back in 2012. We have built a couple of satellite services, but we haven’t created a strategy to adopt the microservice architecture systematically. As the system becomes more complex and the team grows, we moved to a microservice architecture in early 2018. In this post, we want to</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>这就是硅谷</title>
      <link>https://tonyxu.io/zh/reads/2019-03-06/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tonyxu.io/zh/reads/2019-03-06/</guid>
      <description>This Is Silicon Valley (onezero.medium.com) Everyone wears Patagonia and North Face, everyone has AirPods hanging from their ears, and everyone goes to Lake Tahoe on weekends. And everyone talks about the same things: startups, blockchain, machine learning, and startups with blockchain and machine learning. As Jeffrey Hammerbacher, a former Facebook executive, told Bloomberg, “The best minds of my generation are thinking about how to make people click</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>协调世界时已经足够了，是吗?</title>
      <link>https://tonyxu.io/zh/reads/2019-03-03/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tonyxu.io/zh/reads/2019-03-03/</guid>
      <description>UTC is Enough for Everyone, Right? (zachholman.com) It turns out humans have had a long, long history of poorly dealing with time, so when you hammer your head against the wall trying to deal with a timezone bug, well, you’re just the last in a long, long line of human beings that are terrible at all this! Congrats. You’re pretty</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>